northampton.gov.uk 2015-09-07

# Terms and disclaimer | Northampton Borough Council

**Cookies**

**Copyright  
** All material on this website, including text and graphics, is copyright Northampton Borough Council unless otherwise stated. 

The text and graphic content of this web site may be used, printed and distributed ONLY under the following conditions: 

  * The content of the site is used for non-commercial purposes only
  * Copyright information is displayed (© Copyright [year] Northampton Borough Council)
  * The content is not modified

**Disclaimer  
** While every care has been taken in the compilation of this information, Northampton Borough Council will not be held responsible for any loss, damage or inconvenience caused as a result of inaccuracy or error within these pages. 

Northampton Borough Council does not endorse any external linked sites and is not responsible for their content. 

**Data Quality  
** Northampton Borough Council is committed to the highest standards of quality of information. 

If you are aware that there are any errors in the information provided please notify us by emailing 

**Information about Northampton Borough Council and our Website  
** Our privacy policy covers Northampton Borough Council and its website. Should you have any queries about the site, you can contact us by using our online form <http://www.northampton.gov.uk/contactthecouncil>

Accessing Northampton Borough Council's Website   
You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data to obtain information about the Northampton Borough Council services and activities. 

What personal information do we collect?   
To use our online services we will ask you to register your name, email address and other relevant personal details. We will also collect information from you if you complete any other forms on our site or if you contact us with comments or specific requests. This information will only be used for the intended purpose and should we wish to use it for any other purpose, we will ask for your permission first. 

Collecting information automatically   
In order that we can improve our online services we will collect information about your visits to www.northampton.gov.uk. These statistics do not contain personal data and cannot be traced back to an individual. 

**We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.**

Disclosure   
We will only use personal information you send us for the purposes for which you provide it. 

**We will only hold your information for as long as necessary for these purposes and will not pass it on to any other parties, except where required to carry out our duties and functions as a local authority.**

**All employees and subsidiaries who may have access to your personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.**

**All your communications to us are protected against unauthorized access by third parties.**

Confidentiality/Security   
All the personal data stored on this website is recorded in a secure database. 

**All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.**

**We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to government institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.**

**Any payment or financial information is transmitted using 128bit Encryption using THWATE SSL certification.**

Data Protection   
We will treat any personal information by which you can be in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998. If you have an enquiry or concern regarding the processing of personal data by Northampton Borough Council, please contact: 

**Information Access Requests  
Northampton Borough Council   
The Guildhall   
St Giles Square   
Northampton   
NN1 1DE**

**You can ask us for information we may hold about you by writing to the above address. We will inform you within 40 days if we store any personal information about you.**

**You may also write to the above address to request a copy of your information and we will provide you with a legible copy of the personal data which we keep about you and to which you are entitled. This will be sent to you within 40 days of your request- although we may require proof of your identity and information to locate your personal data.**

**There may be a small charge for this information.**
